Guide to the Jake Austen Zine Collection 1972-2013
University of Chicago Library
Austen, Jake. Zine Collection
1972-2013
11 linear feet (22 boxes)
Hanna Holborn Gray Special Collections Research Center University of Chicago Library 1100 East 57th Street Chicago, Illinois 60637 U.S.A.
Zines collected by Jake Austen, founder of Roctober Magazine. The zines were collected in Chicago at fairs and other events, and by mail from around the country, often in trade for issues of Roctober.
Information on Use
Access
This collection is open for research.
Subject Headings
Zines; Periodicals; Underground periodicals; Fanzines; Underground press
Related Resources
Browse finding aids by topic.
INVENTORY
- redguard (editor), Absent cause, 1, 2008 (Box 1, Folder 1)
- redguard (editor), Absent cause, 2 - Duality, 2009 (Box 1, Folder 1)
- redguard (editor), Absent cause, 4 - 'Survival', 2010 (Box 1, Folder 1)
- Vaughn, Andrea (editor), Absolute beginners, undated (Box 1, Folder 2)
- Action four, 2000 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- Rottkamp, Tom, America's fan, September 1993 (Box 1, Folder 4)
- Rottkamp, Tom, America's fan, October 1993 (Box 1, Folder 4)
- Harvey, James D. (executive editor); Donato, Joe (editor), AfterFX, 0 - The debut, undated (Box 1, Folder 5)
- Harvey, James D., AfterFX, 12 - War! What is it good for?, undated (Box 1, Folder 5)
- Agenda, The complete adventures of Curious George W., May/June 2001 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- Ain't nothing like fuckin' moonshine, 7 - The umbrella and the skateboard, undated (Box 1, Folder 7)
- Ain't nothing like fuckin' moonshine, 8 - Upon the grassy knoll, undated, No. 332 of 500 copies (Box 1, Folder 7)
- Ain't nothing like fuckin' moonshine, 9 - A graphic emporium, undated (Box 1, Folder 7)
- Ain't nothing like fuckin' moonshine, 10 - The graphic emporium, Summer 1995 (Box 1, Folder 7)
- Ain't nothing like fuckin' moonshine, 11 - Monkeys and bananas, Summer/fall 1996 (Box 1, Folder 7)
- Ain't nothing like fuckin' moonshine, 12 - Insects inventions, undated (Box 1, Folder 7)
- Ain't nothing like fuckin' moonshine, 14 - Caves, Summer 2000 (Box 1, Folder 7)
- Ain't nothing like fuckin' moonshine, 14 - Caves, Summer 2000 (Box 1, Folder 7)
- Meno, Joe, Airports of light, 2006 (Box 1, Folder 8)
- Alco-beat, 6, undated, Inscribed by the author (Box 1, Folder 9)
- Alco-beat, 13, undated (Box 1, Folder 9)
- Sam; Raf, Alley connoisseur, [1], 2012 (Box 1, Folder 10)
- Sam; Raf, Alley connoisseur, 2, 2013 (Box 1, Folder 10)
- Aluminum sauce delight, 1, Fall 1999 (Box 1, Folder 11)
- Joy, Elissa, American barricade, 1, undated (Box 1, Folder 12)
- American journal of slot car sciences, 1991, Inscribed by the author (Box 1, Folder 13)
- Sinoun, The anatomic air review, 2005?, Has laid in a printed letter from the author (Box 1, Folder 14)
- Sutton, Dan (editor), Anhedonia, Fall 1994 (Box 2, Folder 1)
- Sutton, Dan (editor), Anhedonia, Spring 1995 (Box 2, Folder 1)
- Sutton, Dan (editor), Anhedonia, Summer 1995 (Box 2, Folder 1)
- Arsenault, Marc (editor), Andy's chair, 1, 1992, Fourth printing. No. 9 of 93 copies (Box 2, Folder 2)
- Arsenault, Marc (editor), Andy's chair, 3, 1994 (Box 2, Folder 2)
- Zink, Nell, Animal review, 6, June 1994, Inscribed by the author (Box 2, Folder 3)
- Zink, Nell, Animal review, 7 - Special parasite edition, September 1994 (Box 2, Folder 3)
- Zink, Nell, Animal review, 10 - The Wally memorial edition, October 1995 (Box 2, Folder 3)
- Zink, Nell, Animal review, 11 - Special unreliable edition, March 1996 (Box 2, Folder 3)
- Zink, Nell, Animal review, 14 - Journey to the west, April 1997 (Box 2, Folder 3)
- Zink, Nell, Animal review, 15 - The final issue, September 1997 (Box 2, Folder 3)
- Answer me, 3, 1993 (Box 2, Folder 4)
- Anti-racist news, December 1998 (Box 2, Folder 5)
- Anti-zine, 33 1/3, February 1997 (Box 2, Folder 6)
- Polysorbate, Rich, Ark spurting blood, 1, Summer 2000, Has three folded leaves laid in (Box 2, Folder 7)
- Art detox, 2010 (Box 2, Folder 8)
- Aunt Franne, 1, 1995 (Box 2, Folder 9)
- Aunt Franne, 2, 1995 (Box 2, Folder 9)
- Aunt Franne, 3, 1996 (Box 2, Folder 9)
- Aunt Franne, 5, Spring/summer 1997 (Box 2, Folder 9)
- Baby split bowling news, vol. 3, no. 1, 1992 (Box 2, Folder 10)
- Baby split bowling news, vol. 3, no. 4, November 1992 (Box 2, Folder 10)
- Baby split bowling news, vol. 4, no. 1, January 1995 (Box 2, Folder 10)
- Bad cards of the pros, 1, undated (Box 2, Folder 11)
- Aspenwall, Zeke (editor), Bad news and kneiner, 33?, undated (Box 2, Folder 12)
- Baitline, 43, May/June 2013 (Box 2, Folder 13)
- Bananafish, undated (Box 2, Folder 14)
- Bogard, Seth, Applebee's, 4, undated (Box 2, Folder 15)
- Bogard, Seth, Applebee's, 5, 1996 (Box 2, Folder 15)
- Backflip chokehold brainclaw dropkick, 1996? (Box 3, Folder 1)
- Beens for teen, 6 - Mac n me splitzine, undated (Box 3, Folder 2)
- Drea, A.B. (editor), The banana king, "vol. 1, no. 1, Summer 2004 (Box 3, Folder 3)
- Morgan, Adam, The beautiful underworld super reef zine, The millenium issue, 2000? (Box 3, Folder 4)
- Beer zine, 1997 (Box 3, Folder 5)
- Darby (editor), Ben is dead, 1993 (Box 3, Folder 6)
- Darby (editor), Ben is dead, 1993 (Box 3, Folder 6)
- Darby (editor), Ben is dead, 23, Spring 1994 (Box 3, Folder 6)
- Darby (editor), Ben is dead, 24, Summer 1994 (Box 3, Folder 7)
- Darby (editor), Ben is dead, 25 - Retro hell part one, 1995 (Box 3, Folder 7)
- Darby (editor), Ben is dead, 26 - Retro hell part two, Winter 1996 (Box 3, Folder 8)
- Darby (editor), Ben is dead, 27 - Retro hell part three, 1998 (Box 3, Folder 8)
- Darby (editor), Ben is dead, 28, 1997 (Box 3, Folder 9)
- Darby (editor), Ben is dead, 29, 1998 (Box 3, Folder 9)
- Priddle, Ross, Dominate the mind, 2011 (Box 3, Folder 10)
- Best zine ever, 4, 2005 (Box 3, Folder 11)
- Best zine ever, 5, 2006 (Box 3, Folder 11)
- Lennard, Dann, Betty paginated, 14, February/March 1996 (Box 3, Folder 12)
- Lennard, Dann, Betty paginated, 15, Winter 1996 (Box 3, Folder 12)
- Lennard, Dann, Betty paginated, 16, Summer 1996 (Box 3, Folder 12)
- Lennard, Dann, Betty paginated, 17, Winter 1997 (Box 3, Folder 12)
- Lennard, Dann, Betty paginated, 18, Mid-1998 (Box 3, Folder 12)
- Lennard, Dann, Betty paginated, 19, 1999 (Box 3, Folder 12)
- Lennard, Dann, Betty paginated, 20, undated (Box 3, Folder 12)
- Lennard, Dann, Betty paginated, 21, undated (Box 3, Folder 13)
- Lennard, Dann, Betty paginated, 22, undated (Box 3, Folder 13)
- Lennard, Dann, Betty paginated, 23, undated (Box 3, Folder 13)
- Lennard, Dann, Betty paginated, 24, Autumn 2002 (Box 4, Folder 1)
- Lennard, Dann, Betty paginated, 25, October 2002 (Box 4, Folder 1)
- Lennard, Dann, Betty paginated, 26, Spring 2003 (Box 4, Folder 1)
- Lennard, Dann, Betty paginated, 27, August/September 2004 (Box 4, Folder 1)
- Lennard, Dann, Betty paginated, 28, Autumn 2005 (Box 4, Folder 2)
- Lennard, Dann, Betty paginated, 29, Winter 2006 (Box 4, Folder 2)
- Lennard, Dann, Betty paginated, 30, Autumn 2007 (Box 4, Folder 2)
- Lennard, Dann, Betty paginated, 31, Winter 2010 (Box 4, Folder 2)
- Lennard, Dann, Betty paginated, 32, Winter 2011 (Box 4, Folder 2)
- Lennard, Dann, BP Jr, 1, Summer 2007/2009 (Box 4, Folder 3)
- Smith, Aaron Lake, Big hands, 9, 2011 (Box 4, Folder 4)
- Omlid, Steve (editor), Black sheets, 9 - Whore moan: the sex work issue, 1996 (Box 4, Folder 5)
- Brent, Bill (editor), Black sheets, 10 - Beastiality and glamour, 1997 (Box 4, Folder 5)
- Brent, Bill (editor), Black sheets, 11 - Bad sex, 1997 (Box 4, Folder 5)
- Maggio, Charles; Hayunga, Ron; Roman, Anthony, Blame it on the fat kid, 1, undated (Box 4, Folder 6)
- H., Janelle, Tales of blarg, 7, undated (Box 4, Folder 7)
- MacDonald, Love, Blighted blighter, undated (Box 4, Folder 8)
- Paul, Louis (publisher); Stock, H. A. (editor), Blood times, "vol. 1, no. 17/18, 1991 (Box 4, Folder 9)
- de Rais, Basil, Blow up, 1, undated (Box 4, Folder 10)
- Lee, Aaron, Blue persuasion, December 1992 (Box 4, Folder 11)
- Lee, Aaron, Blue persuasion, March 1993 (Box 4, Folder 11)
- Lee, Aaron, Blue persuasion, 3, undated (Box 4, Folder 11)
- Lee, Aaron, Blue persuasion, 4, 1993 (Box 4, Folder 11)
- Kulick, Stephanie, Blunderbuss, 1, 1993 (Box 4, Folder 12)
- Bowel movement quarterly, 4, 1998 (Box 4, Folder 13)
- Bob Rees, 1993 (Box 4, Folder 14)
- Johnson, Mike (publisher); Kamper, Bill (publisher), Bonus, "vol. 1, no. 2, 1992 (Box 4, Folder 15)
- Boredom, undated (Box 4, Folder 16)
- Bovine gazette, "vol. 2, no. 8, December/January 1993/1994 (Box 5, Folder 1)
- Bovine gazette, vol. 3. no. 4, April/May 1995 (Box 5, Folder 1)
- Meline, Gabe, "Boy, does high school ever suck, Final issue, Fall 1992 (Box 5, Folder 2)
- Wrekk, Alex, Brainscan, 19, December 2002 (Box 5, Folder 3)
- Peppermint, Tyler (editor), Bruce on a stick, 2, July 1993 (Box 5, Folder 4)
- BRV, undated (Box 5, Folder 5)
- Bubba's live bait, 8, undated (Box 5, Folder 6)
- Grover, Jenni, Buffalo speedway, 4, September/October 1996 (Box 5, Folder 7)
- Grover, Jenni, Buffalo speedway, 5, December 1996/January 1997, Has two mini comics laid in (Box 5, Folder 7)
- Bell, Jason, Buffalo speedway, 6, undated, Has mini comic by Dave Wells and special mini book laid in (Box 5, Folder 7)
- Fusselman, Amy, Bunny rabbit, 2, undated (Box 5, Folder 8)
- Tolentino, Noel (editor), Bunnyhop, 6 - The normal issue, 1995 (Box 5, Folder 9)
- Tolentino, Noel (editor), Bunnyhop, 7 - The soft and fluffy issue, 1996 (Box 5, Folder 9)
- Dayton, Robert, Bunyon, 7, undated (Box 5, Folder 10)
- Dayton, Robert, Bunyon, 9, undated (Box 5, Folder 10)
- Burian, Al, Burn collector, 12, undated (Box 5, Folder 11)
- Burian, Al, Burn collector, 15, undated (Box 5, Folder 11)
- Burian, Al, Burn collector, 15, undated (Box 5, Folder 11)
- Cacophony, Mike, Cacophony, 3, August 2009 (Box 5, Folder 12)
- Cacophony, Mike, Cacophony, 6, undated (Box 5, Folder 12)
- Cacophony, Mike, Frostbite, 1, undated (Box 5, Folder 13)
- Cheap and raunchy, undated (Box 5, Folder 14)
- Cheap and raunchy, September 2008 (Box 5, Folder 14)
- Humpston, Wes, Can't grow up, March 2011 (Box 5, Folder 15)
- Cheer the eff up, 3, undated (Box 5, Folder 16)
- Oss, Kay, [Bullshit], 1, undated, Has laid in a postcard inscribed by the author to Jake Austen (Box 5, Folder 17)
- Rowe, Chip, Chip's closet cleaner, 13, 1996 (Box 6, Folder 1)
- Chili says what's hot, October 1993 (Box 6, Folder 2)
- Kelly, Dan (editor-in-chief), Chum magazine, 1, Fall 1994 (Box 6, Folder 3)
- Kelly, Dan (editor-in-chief), Chum magazine, 2 - Ceci ne'st pas une revue, 1995 (Box 6, Folder 3)
- Kelly, Dan (editor-in-chief), Chum magazine, 3 - Chicago: city of the damned, 1996 (Box 6, Folder 3)
- The CIA makes science fiction unexciting, "1 - The assassination of Martin Luther King,, undated (Box 6, Folder 4)
- The CIA makes science fiction unexciting, "2 - Chemical biological weapons, CIA documents about the AIDS virus, and "cures" killing faster than AIDS, undated (Box 6, Folder 4)
- Mason, Gena, The CIA makes science fiction unexciting, "3 - A look at the way the PATRIOT act of post 9/11 "security" changed our civil liberties and infringed upon basic American rights, 2005 (Box 6, Folder 4)
- Smith, Abner, The CIA makes science fiction unexciting, 4 - The FBI assassination of Puerto Rican independence leader Filberto Ojeda Rios, undated (Box 6, Folder 4)
- The CIA makes science fiction unexciting, 5 - Things you may not know about Iran/Contra, undated (Box 6, Folder 4)
- Palermo, Giles (editor), The cimarron weekend, 5, 1998 (Box 6, Folder 5)
- Dunlap, David L. Jr. (editor); Palermo, Giles, The cimarron weekend, 6, undated (Box 6, Folder 5)
- Dunlap, David L. Jr.; Earles, Andrew Scott, The cimarron weekend, 6.045328937, undated (Box 6, Folder 5)
- Dunlap, David L. Jr.; Earles, Andrew Scott, The cimarron weekend, 7, undated (Box 6, Folder 5)
- Gasior, Lawrence, Classic television, April 1996 (Box 6, Folder 6)
- Gasior, Lawrence, Classic television, October 1997 (Box 6, Folder 6)
- Chilson, John, Schlock: the journal of low-brow cinema and culture, 8, undated (Box 6, Folder 7)
- Chilson, John, Schlock: the journal of low-brow cinema and culture, 9, undated (Box 6, Folder 7)
- Chilson, John, Schlock: the journal of low-brow cinema and culture, 11, undated (Box 6, Folder 7)
- Chilson, John, Schlock: the journal of low-brow cinema and culture, 12, undated (Box 6, Folder 7)
- Chilson, John, Schlock: the journal of low-brow cinema and culture, 13, undated (Box 6, Folder 7)
- Chilson, John, Schlock: the journal of low-brow cinema and culture, 14, undated (Box 6, Folder 7)
- Chilson, John, Schlock: the journal of low-brow cinema and culture, 15, undated (Box 6, Folder 7)
- Chilson, John, Schlock: the journal of low-brow cinema and culture, 17, undated (Box 6, Folder 7)
- Chilson, John, Schlock: the journal of low-brow cinema and culture, 18, undated (Box 6, Folder 7)
- Chilson, John, Schlock: the journal of low-brow cinema and culture, 19, undated (Box 6, Folder 7)
- Chilson, John, Schlock: the journal of low-brow cinema and culture, 20, undated (Box 6, Folder 7)
- Chilson, John, Schlock: the journal of low-brow cinema and culture, 21, undated (Box 6, Folder 7)
- Chilson, John, Schlock: the journal of low-brow cinema and culture, 22, undated (Box 6, Folder 7)
- Chilson, John, Schlock: the journal of low-brow cinema and culture, 25, undated (Box 6, Folder 7)
- Lorenze, Marie, Raymond Raymond: the boy with the tail and other stories, undated (Box 6, Folder 8)
- Cometbus, Aaron, Cometbus, 27, undated (Box 6, Folder 9)
- Cometbus, Aaron, Cometbus, 29, Winter 1992-1993 (Box 6, Folder 9)
- Cometbus, Aaron, Cometbus, 30 - The Berkeley issue, Summer 1993 (Box 6, Folder 9)
- Adbul-Haqq, Lionel, Community cultivations: reviews from the video library, "vol. 5, no. 23, January-March 1997 (Box 6, Folder 10)
- Pohlen, Jerome, "Cool spots, USA, version 1 - Indiana, August 1993 (Box 6, Folder 11)
- Kelly, Dan, Cop porn, 1997 (Box 6, Folder 12)
- Koyen, Jeff, Crank, 2, 1994 (Box 6, Folder 13)
- Koyen, Jeff, Crank, 6, 1997 (Box 6, Folder 13)
- Ruspantini, Michael, Creepy Mike's omnibus of fun, 1, 1995 (Box 6, Folder 14)
- Ruspantini, Michael, Creepy Mike's omnibus of fun, 2, 1996 (Box 6, Folder 14)
- Ruspantini, Michael, Creepy Mike's omnibus of fun, 3, 1996 (Box 6, Folder 14)
- Ruspantini, Michael, Creepy Mike's omnibus of fun, 4, 1996 (Box 6, Folder 14)
- Ruspantini, Michael, Creepy Mike's omnibus of fun, 5, April 1997 (Box 6, Folder 14)
- Maynard, Mike; Lao, Linette, Crimewave U.S.A., 9, 1998 (Box 7, Folder 1)
- Maynard, Mike; Lao, Linette, Crimewave U.S.A., 12, 1999 (Box 7, Folder 1)
- Maynard, Mike; Lao, Linette, Crimewave U.S.A., 13, 2001 (Box 7, Folder 1)
- Tandy, William P., Criminally yours, 2007 (Box 7, Folder 2)
- Edelstein, Johny; Clemens, Sylvia, Crucial variable, 1, undated (Box 7, Folder 3)
- Edelstein, Johny; Clemens, Sylvia, Crucial variable, 2, undated (Box 7, Folder 3)
- Edelstein, Johny; Clemens, Sylvia, Crucial variable, 3, undated (Box 7, Folder 3)
- Kelly, Laura (editor), Crying clown, 1, 1996, Inscribed to Jake Austen (Box 7, Folder 4)
- Kelly, Laura (editor), Crying clown, 2 - The second clown, January 1997 (Box 7, Folder 4)
- Cultural correspondence, no. 10-11 - Surrealism and its popular accomplices, Fall 1979 (Box 7, Folder 5)
- Partlow, Mia; Hoerger, Michael, The curious case of the communist Jell-O box: the execution of Julius & Ethel Rosenberg, undated (Box 7, Folder 6)
- Etchen, Russell, Dance party, 2, Summer/Fall 1998 (Box 7, Folder 7)
- Kelly, Dan, Danger!, 1, undated (Box 7, Folder 8)
- Kelly, Dan, Danger!, 2, undated (Box 7, Folder 8)
- Edelstein, Johny, Dan the knobhead, 1, 1993 (Box 7, Folder 9)
- Vnuk, Helen; Lennard, Dann, A dash of Jones, 3, Spring 2010 (Box 7, Folder 10)
- Vnuk, Helen; Lennard, Dann, A dash of Jones, 5, Spring 2012 (Box 7, Folder 10)
- Bay, Christopher D., David Letterman - miscellaneous appearances, undated (Box 7, Folder 11)
- Dead air: official zine of the Windy City Bicycle Messengers Association, Mid-January 1997 (Box 7, Folder 12)
- Dead air: official zine of the Windy City Bicycle Messengers Association, 6, December 1997 (Box 7, Folder 12)
- Dead air: official zine of the Windy City Bicycle Messengers Association, 7, February 1998 (Box 7, Folder 12)
- Daniels, James (editor), Dead air: official zine of the Windy City Bicycle Messengers Association, 8, April 1998 (Box 7, Folder 12)
- Daniels, James (editor), Dead air: official zine of the Windy City Bicycle Messengers Association, 9, June 1998 (Box 7, Folder 12)
- mowgli, Dead dynasty, undated, No. 20 of 50 copies (Box 7, Folder 13)
- Meyer, Christopher, Defeated by Maryland, 2008 (Box 7, Folder 14)
- Justin; Tina, Desperate love, 1, June 2001 (Box 7, Folder 15)
- Hessig, Janelle, Desperate times, 8, July 2000 (Box 7, Folder 16)
- Destroying angels, 6, undated (Box 7, Folder 17)
- Destroying angels, 8, September 2005 (Box 7, Folder 17)
- Summers, Jill, Diagnosis of sadness, undated (Box 7, Folder 18)
- Diamondbacks, 2001, Has CD laid in (Box 7, Folder 19)
- Bogard, Seth; Cooper, Layla, Diorama, 1, undated (Box 7, Folder 20)
- Dirt, 5, Easter 1993, Has laid in a color photcopy of a painting of the cross of souls, Eat Yourself a Pie - January 1993, Easter streamers, and a shotgun casing (Box 7, Folder 21)
- Jordan, Pete, Dishwasher, "7 - The Alaska gig, 8 - Boulder, Colorado, undated (Box 8, Folder 1)
- Jordan, Pete, Dishwasher, 9, undated (Box 8, Folder 1)
- Jordan, Pete, Dishwasher, 10, undated (Box 8, Folder 1)
- Jordan, Pete, Dishwasher, 11, undated (Box 8, Folder 1)
- Jordan, Pete, Dishwasher, 12, undated (Box 8, Folder 1)
- Jordan, Pete, Dishwasher, 13 - The northwest tour, undated (Box 8, Folder 1)
- Jordan, Pete, Dishwasher, 14, undated (Box 8, Folder 1)
- Jordan, Pete, Dishwasher, 15, undated (Box 8, Folder 1)
- Jordan, Pete, Dishwasher, 16, undated (Box 8, Folder 1)
- Ann, Rebecca, Distracted by the stars, 3, 1998? (Box 8, Folder 2)
- Goodman, Maria, Don't say uh-oh!, 10, March 1995 (Box 8, Folder 3)
- Donut frenzy, 3, 1993 (Box 8, Folder 4)
- Crabb, Cindy, Doris, 23, 2006 (Box 8, Folder 5)
- Dork, Denise, Dork magazine, 11, undated (Box 8, Folder 6)
- Holzner, Dan, Dream scene magazine, 1996 (Box 8, Folder 7)
- Dayton, Robert (editor); Lawrence, Julian (editor), Drippy gazette, vol. 1, no. 3, November 1999, Inscribed by editor Robert Dayton to Jake Austen (Box 8, Folder 8)
- Dayton, Robert (editor); Lawrence, Julian (editor), Drippy gazette, vol. 2, no. 6, March 2000, Inscribed by editor Robert Dayton to Jake Austen (Box 8, Folder 8)
- Dayton, Robert (editor); Lawrence, Julian (editor); Smolenski, Lester (editor), Drippy gazette, "vol. 2, no. 8, May 2000, Inscribed by editor Robert Dayton (Box 8, Folder 8)
- Dayton, Robert (editor); Lawrence, Julian (editor); Smolenski, Lester (editor), Drippy gazette, "vol. 2, no. 9, June 2000 (Box 8, Folder 8)
- Dayton, Robert (editor); Lawrence, Julian (editor); Smolenski, Lester (editor), Drippy gazette, "vol. 2, no. 10, July 2000 (Box 8, Folder 8)
- Dayton, Robert (editor); Lawrence, Julian (editor); Smolenski, Lester (editor), Drippy gazette, "vol. 2, no. 11, September 2000 (Box 8, Folder 8)
- Dayton, Robert (editor); Lawrence, Julian (editor); Smolenski, Lester (editor), Drippy gazette, "vol. 2, no. 12, "November/December 2000, January 2001" (Box 8, Folder 8)
- Dumpsterland, Dave, Dumpsterland, 6, undated (Box 8, Folder 9)
- Greenberger, David, The duplex planet, 46, March 1983 (Box 8, Folder 10)
- Greenberger, David, The duplex planet, 52, 1983 (Box 8, Folder 10)
- Greenberger, David, The duplex planet, 65, June 1985 (Box 8, Folder 10)
- Greenberger, David, The duplex planet, 66, 1985 (Box 8, Folder 10)
- Greenberger, David, The duplex planet, 20 - Newly revised and expanded edition of the 1981 classic, 1986 (Box 8, Folder 10)
- Greenberger, David, The duplex planet, 72, 1986 (Box 8, Folder 10)
- Greenberger, David, The duplex planet, 74, 1986 (Box 8, Folder 10)
- Greenberger, David, The duplex planet, 89, 1987 (Box 8, Folder 10)
- Greenberger, David, The duplex planet, 100, 1989 (Box 8, Folder 10)
- Greenberger, David, The duplex planet, 102, 1989 (Box 8, Folder 10)
- Greenberger, David, The duplex planet, 103, 1989 (Box 8, Folder 10)
- Greenberger, David, The duplex planet, 106, 1990 (Box 8, Folder 10)
- Greenberger, David, The duplex planet, Happy birthday to you!, 1992, "Portions of this special edition of The Duplex Planet originally appeared in issue #41, October, 1982." (Box 8, Folder 10)
- Greenberger, David, The duplex planet, 122, 1992 (Box 8, Folder 10)
- Greenberger, David, The duplex planet, 123, 1992 (Box 8, Folder 10)
- Greenberger, David, The duplex planet, 124, 1993 (Box 8, Folder 10)
- Greenberger, David, The duplex planet, 125, 1993, Inscribed by the author to Jake Austen (Box 8, Folder 10)
- Greenberger, David, The duplex planet, 126, 1993, Inscribed by the author to Jake Austen (Box 8, Folder 10)
- Greenberger, David, The duplex planet, 128, 1993 (Box 8, Folder 10)
- Greenberger, David, The duplex planet, 129, 1993, Inscribed by the author to Jake Austen (Box 8, Folder 10)
- Greenberger, David, The duplex planet, 131, 1994 (Box 8, Folder 10)
- Greenberger, David, The duplex planet, 134, 1994, Inscribed by the author to Jake Austen (Box 8, Folder 10)
- Greenberger, David, The duplex planet, 138, 1995 (Box 8, Folder 10)
- Greenberger, David, The duplex planet, 139, 1995 (Box 8, Folder 10)
- Greenberger, David, The duplex planet, 140, 1996, Inscribed by the author to Jake Austen (Box 8, Folder 10)
- Greenberger, David, The duplex planet, 141, 1996 (Box 8, Folder 10)
- Greenberger, David, The duplex planet, 142, 1996 (Box 8, Folder 11)
- Greenberger, David, The duplex planet, 146, 1997 (Box 8, Folder 11)
- Greenberger, David, The duplex planet, 147, 1997 (Box 8, Folder 11)
- Greenberger, David, The duplex planet, 148, 1997 (Box 8, Folder 11)
- Greenberger, David, The duplex planet, 149, 1998 (Box 8, Folder 11)
- Greenberger, David, The duplex planet, 150, 1998 (Box 8, Folder 11)
- Greenberger, David, The duplex planet, 151, 1998 (Box 8, Folder 11)
- Greenberger, David, The duplex planet, 152, 1998 (Box 8, Folder 11)
- Greenberger, David, The duplex planet, 153, 1999 (Box 8, Folder 11)
- Greenberger, David, The duplex planet, 154, 1999 (Box 9, Folder 1)
- Greenberger, David, The duplex planet, 155, 1999 (Box 9, Folder 1)
- Greenberger, David, The duplex planet, 156, 2000 (Box 9, Folder 1)
- Greenberger, David, The duplex planet, 157, 2000 (Box 9, Folder 1)
- Greenberger, David, The duplex planet, 158, 2000 (Box 9, Folder 1)
- Greenberger, David, The duplex planet, 159, 2001 (Box 9, Folder 1)
- Greenberger, David, The duplex planet, 160, 2001 (Box 9, Folder 1)
- Greenberger, David, The duplex planet, 161, 2001 (Box 9, Folder 1)
- Greenberger, David, The duplex planet, 162, 2002 (Box 9, Folder 1)
- Greenberger, David, The duplex planet, 163, 2002 (Box 9, Folder 1)
- Greenberger, David, The duplex planet, 164, 2002 (Box 9, Folder 1)
- Greenberger, David, The duplex planet, 165, 2003 (Box 9, Folder 1)
- Greenberger, David, The duplex planet, 166, 2003 (Box 9, Folder 1)
- Greenberger, David, The duplex planet, 167, 2003 (Box 9, Folder 1)
- Greenberger, David, The duplex planet, 167, 2003 (Box 9, Folder 1)
- Greenberger, David, The duplex planet, 168, 2003 (Box 9, Folder 1)
- Greenberger, David, The duplex planet, 169, 2003 (Box 9, Folder 1)
- Greenberger, David, The duplex planet, 170, 2004 (Box 9, Folder 2)
- Greenberger, David, The duplex planet, 171, 2004 (Box 9, Folder 2)
- Greenberger, David, The duplex planet, 172, 2005 (Box 9, Folder 2)
- Greenberger, David, The duplex planet, 173, 2005 (Box 9, Folder 2)
- Greenberger, David, The duplex planet, 174, 2005 (Box 9, Folder 2)
- Greenberger, David, The duplex planet, 175, 2005 (Box 9, Folder 2)
- Greenberger, David, The duplex planet, 176, 2006 (Box 9, Folder 2)
- Greenberger, David, The duplex planet, 177, 2006 (Box 9, Folder 2)